And okay, perfect.
好，完美
If we hit compile a fun meat outsole,
如果我们点击编译 FundMe.sol
we do indeed see that it's passing compliation.
我们确实看到它通过了编译
However, there's a bit of an issue here,
不过，这里还有一个小问题
right now, anybody can withdraw from this contract.
现在，无论是谁都可以从这个合约提款
So anybody can fund, which is what we want.
任何人都可以出资，这是我们想要的
But we don't want anyone to be able to withdraw.
但我们不希望随便谁都能提款
We only want the person who's collecting the funds to be able to actually withdraw the funds.
我们只想让那个募集资金的人能够真正提取资金
So how do we set this up so that the withdraw function is only called by the owner of this contract?
所以我们该怎么设置才能够让这个 withdraw 函数只能被合约的拥有者调用呢？
Well, to do that, we're going to set up a couple new functions.
为此，我们要建立一组新函数
So when we deploy this contract,
所以，当我们部署这个合约时
we want to automatically set it up
我们想让它自动进行设置
so that whomever deploys this contract is going to be the owner of this contract.
这样，无论是谁部署了这个合约都将成为合约的拥有者
And then we can do some parameters to set it up so that only the owner of this contract can call the withdrawal function.
然后我们就可以用一些参数，设定只有合约的拥有者才能调用 withdraw 函数
So how would we do that?
所以我们该怎么做呢
Well, maybe we can create a function called like, call me right away.
也许我们可以创建一个这样的函数，称为 callMeRightAway
And right after we deploy this contract, we call this call me right away function,
然后在我们部署合约后，立刻调用这个 callMeRightAway 函数
which will set up us as the owner.
这样我们就能成为合约的拥有者了
Now that's going to take two transactions.
不过这样就必须发起两次交易
And that would be really annoying if we had to do that.
如果我们不得不这样做的话，那未免也太麻烦了
So instead, solidity has something called a constructor.
因此，solidity 提供了一种称为构造函数(constructor)的东西
And if you're familiar with other programming language,
如果你熟悉其它编程语言的话，
a constructor is exactly the same as other programming languages.
这个构造函数与其它编程语言的完全相同
constructor is going to be the function that gets called when,
构造函数的调用机制是这样的
immediately whenever or you deploy a contract.
它会在你部署合约后立即调用一次
So if I were to deploy Funmi, dot Sol, and I were to say, minimum USD equals to
所以，如果我要部署 FundMe.sol，并且在这里写下 minimumUsd 等于 2
minimum USD would no longer be 50 times one e to the 18th,
minimumUsd 就不再是 50 乘 10 的 18 次方了
it would be immediately updated to two.
它会立即更新为 2
Because constructor is a function that gets immediately called in the same transaction, that we create this contract,
这是因为构造函数在创建合约的那笔交易中被立刻调用了一次
this constructor function is going to be incredibly helpful for us,
这个构造函数对我们来说有很大的用处
because it allows us to set up the contract the way we want it to be.
因为它允许我们以我们想要的方式设置合约
So for example,
举个例子
if we want the withdrawal function to only be able to be called by the owner of this contract,
如果我们想要 withdraw 函数只能被合约的拥有者调用
we can have the constructor set up who the owner of the contract is.
那么我们可以通过构造函数来设置合约的拥有者是谁
So let's create a global variable called address, public owner.
所以我来们创建一个全局变量 address public owner
And then in our constructor,
然后在我们的构造函数内
we'll say the owner is going to be equal to the message dot sender.
我们让 owner 等于 msg.sender
The message that sender of the constructor function
这个构造函数内的 msg.sender
is going to be whoever is deploying the contract.
就是部署这个合约的人
So owner is now going to be whoever deployed this contract.
所以 owner 现在就是部署这个合约的人了
And don't worry, we're going to demo all this very soon
不用担心，我们马上就会进行演示
and show you everything that's going on with ether scan everything,
并向你展示 etherscan 上的一切情况
demoing this all right now might take a little bit of time,
现在就进行演示可能会比较费时
because we're using a test net.
因为要使用测试网络
So if you want to test it all right now, absolutely go for it,
如果你现在测试一下的话，完全可以开始了
but just know, it'll take you a little bit longer to do so.
但你要知道，这样做会比较费你的时间